we have here and in which the bun has been
tenemos acá y en la que el bollo se ha
pronounced
pronunciado
[Music]
[Música]
or rather I didn't know this
o sea que esto no lo sabía yo
thanks speaking clearly that he just
gracias hablando claro que me la acaba
sent it to me on whatsapp
de mandar por whatsapp
wait that I have to tell this
espera que esto lo tengo que contar
and I didn't know this of course what a
y esto no lo sabía
coward
claro que cobarde
what a coward but let's see these things these
qué cobarde pero a ver estas cosas estas
things are also done speaking clearly by
cosas las hace también hablando claro
someone that you I know knows what it means to say
uno que tú yo sabemos sabe que es decir
the thing and you think that by not saying the
la cosa y te crees que por no decir el
name
nombre
no no
no no
that it grows on you by not saying the name
que te crece por no decir el nombre
judicially as if you didn't say anything
judicialmente como si tú no dijeran nada
and let's see it depends on the context you know it
y a ver depende del contexto sabe
depends on the context then the
depende del contexto entonces el
unmentionable no
innombrable no
kiko hernandez first put the
kiko hernández primero puso el
unmentionable Antonio David Antonio
innombrable de antonio david antonio
notice more fortunate and then he has edited it
aviso más afortunado y luego lo ha
or he has edited it to change it he has deleted
o lo ha editado a cambiar lo ha borrado
the return for the voucher to remove the
la vuelta por el vale para quitar el
name
nombre
[Music]
[Música]
but what nonsense god this is
pero qué tontería dios esto es una
nonsense it is at the judicial level it doesn't
chorrada está a nivel judicial no
matter when we know that the context of
importa cuando sabemos que el contexto
course they do this if they do this
claro que esto lo hacen si esto lo hacen
because they think that the fact of not putting
porque se creen que el hecho de no poner
the name in a court is worth you to
el nombre en un juzgado te vale para
say them named it's like I say you  you
decir a ellos nombrado es como digo tú
ask to know if you are speaking in the
pides saber si estás hablando en el
context that the other person has made a
contexto de que el otro te ha hecho un
video of you, he is responding to the video and on
vídeo está respondiendo al vídeo y
top of that you put yourself here like this, the mother of all the problems, the mother of all the problems, it is
encima te pones aquí así la pega madre
necessary that I put the name or that I
hace falta que ponga el nombre o que lo
remove it, stupidity but there is cowardice,
quite estupidez pero haya cobardica
other thanks, speaking clearly, I didn't know it, I
otras gracias hablando claro no lo sabía
would have said it and now he came yesterday to me, I saw
yo lo hubiera dicho y ahora vino ayer a
the response but I didn't see this, but I
la vi la respuesta pero no vi esto pero
doubt it, coward, but Mr. Omar, we confirm, we
dudo cobarde pero don omar de
confirm, the cowardice is already
confirmamos confirmamos la cobardía ya
[Music]
[Música]